<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>INDI</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on INDI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started - A living post</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/05/14/2019-05-14-getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/05/14/2019-05-14-getting-started/</guid>
      <description>After a meeting of the Inland Northwest R User Group on the 27th of April, some of us hung around and started a discussion regarding the &amp;ldquo;grander&amp;rdquo; ideas for how we could work together to expand the impact of a culture of using data for solving social problems. We came up with a list of objectives and how we could address them. This initiative is a result of that discussion. Subsequent discussions on slack lead to the decision regarding a domain name, GitHub handle, and the template for the website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/eventspast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/eventspast/</guid>
      <description> Please scroll through upcoming events in different meetups in and around Spokane   Inland Northwest R User Group   Spokane/CdA Machine Learning Group    PyData Spokane   PyData Tri-Cities     </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>We are a group of folks from the Inland Northwest who work in different companies and universities in different roles. What binds us together is our love for data analysis and the region.
Kenneth Farr III Ken Farr is Product Engineering Manager at 2nd Watch. He has a Master of Science in Computer Science from Eastern Washington University. His love of data and statistics emerged from his curiosity of discovering &amp;lsquo;what is true&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> Are you wondering how your data can be put to better use or are you wondering if there are any additional data that can be collected to make better decisions? </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contests</title>
      <link>/contests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contests/</guid>
      <description> Coming Soon&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Datasets</title>
      <link>/datasets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/datasets/</guid>
      <description> City of Spokane&amp;rsquo;s Open Data: https://my.spokanecity.org/opendata/ Spokane Community Indicators Initiative: http://spokanetrends.org/ Spokane Regional Health District Data and Reports: https://srhd.org/data-and-reports/ Spokane Crime Rates: https://www.neighborhoodscout.com/wa/spokane/crime  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/</guid>
      <description>This is a listing of few upcoming events in the area.
We are following four specific Meetup groups in the Greater Spokane area. Please contact us if you would like to see the schedule of additional meetup groups that are related to our objective listed here.
 Inland Northwest R User Group Python Tri-Cities PyData Spokane Spokane/CdA Machine Learning Group    When  What  Where  Details      07/09/2019 17:30  Beginners Code and Learn (2nd Tuesday of each month)  Richland Public Library, 955 Northgate Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>